<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
    android:paddingLeft="10dp"
    android:paddingRight="10dp"
    android:paddingTop="10dp"
    android:paddingBottom="10dp"
    tools:context=".campus">
    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="vertical">
        <ImageButton
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="10dp"
            android:id="@+id/back"
            android:src="@drawable/ic_arrow_back_black_24dp"
            />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="423dp"
            android:src="@drawable/ambassador"
            />
        <TextView
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:text="Campus Ambassadors, here’s a piece of good news to brighten your day. Due to positively high response and the appreciable enthusiasm we have received in this programme, Reminiscence- The Metallurgical Journey of 80 Years brings you some awesome deals in addition to the benefits promised earlier.
\n1. Data pack will be provided to all the campus ambassadors, for attending the webinar series.
\n2. A digital certificate will be provided as a token of appreciation from our side.
\n\nApart from these, we also have some brilliant perks exclusively for the position holders.
\nI. The Campus Ambassador securing the first position will be rewarded with Rs. 500/- in cash, an Amazon Prime account for 1 month, a Netflix account for 1 month, and a Hotstar VIP account for 1 year.
\nII. The Campus Ambassador securing the second position will be rewarded with Rs. 300/- in cash, an Amazon Prime account for 1 month, and a Netflix account for 1 month.
\nIII. The Campus Ambassador securing the third position will be rewarded with Rs. 200/- in cash and an Amazon Prime account for 1 month.
\n\nLast Date of Hiring: 7th July, 2020"/>
    </LinearLayout>


</ScrollView>